Guide to the Steven Meretzky papers relating to computer game design and interactive fiction history, 1978-2009 M1730
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 3: Design Notebooks
  - Subseries 23: Space Bar, The
    - Space Bar, The - Design - Sraffran (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Space Bar, The - Design - Trisecks (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Space Bar, The - Design - Vedj (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Space Bar, The - Design - Vildroid (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Space Bar, The - Design - Zzazzel (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Space Bar, The - Creative - Interface (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Space Bar, The - Creative - Races and Characters (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Space Bar, The - Creative - Geography (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Space Bar, The - Creative - Background (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Space Bar, The - Final Doc - Concept / Story (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Space Bar, The - Final Doc - Geography (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Space Bar, The - Final Doc - Meta-Game (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Space Bar, The - Final Doc - Flashbacks (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Space Bar, The - Final Doc - Puzzles (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Space Bar, The - Final Doc - Objects (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Space Bar, The - Final Doc - Characters (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Space Bar, The - Final Doc - Art and Audio (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Space Bar, The - Copies of Ron Cobb's Sketches (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Space Bar, The - Universe Awards (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Space Bar, The - Sell Sheets (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Space Bar, The - PR - Errata (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Space Bar, The - TV Show (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Space Bar - Sales and Marketing Stuff (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Space Bar - Development Docs (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Boffo Games Press Kit - Space Bar (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 24: Space Bar II, The
    - Space Bar II, The (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 25: Spellcasting 101
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Hint (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Articles / Reviews (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Packaging (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Bugs / Current (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Art (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Compilations (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - System (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Scenario (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Legal (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Errata (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Spellcasting 101 (Scenario) - Bugs (2 folders) (Box 16, Folders 11-12)
  - Subseries 26: Spellcasting 201
    - Spellcasting 201 (Scenario) - Scenario (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Spellcasting 201 (Scenario) - Legal (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Spellcasting 201 (Scenario) - Art / Music (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Spellcasting 201 (Scenario) - Testing (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Spellcasting 201 (Scenario) - Packaging (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Spellcasting 201 (Scenario) - Schedules (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Spellcasting 201 (Scenario) - Articles / Reviews (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Spellcasting 201 (Scenario) - Hints (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 27: Spellcasting 301
    - Spellcasting 301 - Scenario (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Spellcasting 301 - Art / Music (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Spellcasting 301 - Testing (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Spellcasting 301 - Legal (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Spellcasting 301 - Technical (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Spellcasting 301 - Packaging (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Spellcasting 301 - Hints (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Spellcasting 301 - Articles / Reviews (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 28: Stationfall
    - Stationfall - Compilations (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Stationfall - Scenario (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Stationfall - Current Bugs (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Stationfall - Packaging (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Stationfall - Manual (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Stationfall - Public Relations (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Stationfall - Articles / Reviews (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Stationfall - Outside Testing (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Stationfall - Hintbook (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 29: Superhero League of Hoboken
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Technical (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Scenario (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Geography (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Legal / Financial (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Memos, Etc. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Art / Music (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Testing (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Hintbook (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Background (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Packaging (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Marketing (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken - Reviews (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken Reference Maps [1 of 5] (Tube 1)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken Reference Maps [2 of 5] (Map-folder 2)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken Reference Maps [3 of 5] (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken Reference Maps [4 of 5] (Map-folder 4)
    - Superhero League of Hoboken Reference Maps [5 of 5] (Map-folder 5)
  - Subseries 30: Titanic
    - Titanic: Art (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Titanic: Background Info (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Titanic: Scenario (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Titanic: Design Treatment - December 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Titanic: Research Correspondence & Errata (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Titanic: Errata (Box 42)
  - Subseries 31: Warcraft Adventures
    - Warcraft Adventures (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 32: Wellspring
    - Wellspring (Design) - Background (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Wellspring (Design) - Concept (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Wellspring (Design) - Design Notes (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Wellspring (Design) - Full Design (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Wellspring (Design) - Feedback (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Wellspring (Design) - Business Plan (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 33: Wind in the Willows Background Text
    - Wind in the Willows - Errata (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Wind in the Willows- Movie Script (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text (12 folders) (Box 23, Folder 3-14)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text [5 of 12] (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text [6 of 12] (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text [7 of 12] (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text [8 of 12] (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text [9 of 12] (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text [10 of 12] (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text [11 of 12] (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Wind in the Willows Background Text [12 of 12] (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Wind in the Willows - Treatments (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Wind in the Willows - Design Docs Phase 1 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Wind in the Willows - Prototype Design (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Wind in the Willows - Scheduling (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 34: WorldWinner Games
    - Worldwinner Game Specs - Checkers Challenge (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Worldwinner Game Specs - Chess Challenge (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Worldwinner Game Specs - Super-Tic-Tac-Toe (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Worldwinner Game Specs - Reversi Rampage (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Worldwinner Game Specs - 8-ball Pool (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Worldwinner Game Specs - Press Your Buck / Trivia (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Worldwinner Game Specs - Polar Bowler (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Worldwinner Game Specs - Blackhawk Striker 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Bullseye Darts (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Mine Sweeper (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Free Cell (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Brickout (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Word Cubes (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Shapetris (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Trac-man (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Picture Perfect (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - World Winner Game Specs - 9-ball Pool (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Hangmania (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Golf Solitaire (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Catch 21 / Blackjack Attack (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Swap It! (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Collapse (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Triv! (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Cubis (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Word Mojo (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Blockwerx (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Skillgammon (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Haunted Mines (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Paint Buckets (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - World Winner Game Specs - (new) Spades (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Wheel of Fortune (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Jeopardy! (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Solitaire Rush (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Maze Runner (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Jigsaw Genius (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Pencil Wars (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Crossword Challenge (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Bash 'Em All (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - World Winner Game Specs - Tile City (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 35: Yahtzee
    - Yahtzee - Background (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Yahtzee - Treatments (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Yahtzee - Design Notes (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Yahtzee - Art (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Yahtzee - Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Yahtzee - Budgets / Schedules (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 36: Zork Zero
    - Zork Zero (Scenario) - Game Screens and Map (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Zork Zero (Scenario) - Compilations (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Zork Zero (Scenario): Pre-Design Notes (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Zork Zero (Scenario) - Scenario (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Zork Zero (Scenario) - Graphics and Music (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Zork Zero (Scenario) - Packaging (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Zork Zero (Scenario) - Outside Testing (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Zork Zero (Scenario) - PR (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Zork Zero (Scenario) - Articles / Reviews (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Series 4: Paper Files
  This series is arranged into 16 subseries. Papers include artwork (character sketches, box cover art, maps, and environnment concepts), business documents (corporate logos, web pages, marketing materials, letterheads, human resources materials, and memos), technical documents (ZIL engine, R-Mode Editor), correspondence, newsletters, books, drafts of novels, playthrough notes, hintbooks, posters, and conference materials.
  - Subseries 1: Battleground Zoo
    - Battleground Zoo (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2: Boffo Games
    - Boffo Games - Web Page / Domain (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Boffo Games - "Boffo" References (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Boffo Games - Lease / Space Layout (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Boffo Games - Boffo Logo (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Boffo Games - Postcards (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Boffo Games - Old Phone Lists (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Boffo Games - Stationary, Letterhead (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Boffo Games - Errata (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Boffo Games - Archive (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Boffo Games - Corporate (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Boffo Games - Recruiting (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Boffo Games - Misc. Business (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Boffo Games - Press Release / Founder's Blurb / Info Sheet (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 3: Correspondence
    - Correspondence - Stationfall (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - A Mind Forever Voyaging (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Sorceror (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Leather Goddesses of Phobos (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Leather Goddesses of Phobos 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Superhero League of Hoboken (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Spellcasting 101 / 201 / 301 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Zork Zero (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Other Correspondence - Hodj 'n' Podj (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Other Correspondence - The Space Bar (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Other Correspondence - General (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Other Correspondence - Religious Frothing Nutcake Letters (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Other Correspondence - Books (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Other Correspondence - Customer Support (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - Planetfall (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 4: Harmonix / Disney Music Studio
    - Harmonix / Disney Music Studio (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Subseries 10: Zork Novels
      - Zork Book One: Forces of Krill - Drafts (2 folders) (Box 2, Folders 3-4)
      - Zork Book Two: The Malifestro Quest - Drafts (2 folders) (Box 2, Folders 5-6)
      - Zork Book Three: The Caverns of Doom - Drafts (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Zork Book Four: Conquest of Quendor (2 folders) (Box 3, Folders 2-3)
      - Zork Book Four: Conquest of Quendor - Drafts (2 folders) (Box 3, Folders 2-3)
      - Zork Books - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Zork Books (Most Recent Revisions) - Errata (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Zork Books: Zork Book One (Forces of Krull) Revisions (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Zork Books: Zork Book Two (Malifestro Quest) Revisions (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Zork Books: Zork Book Three (Cavern of Doom) Revisions (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Zork Books: Zork Book Four (Conquest at Quendor) Revisions (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Zork #4 Conquest at Quendor - Book(s), text (Box 36)
      - Zork #3 The Cavern of Doom - Book(s), Text (Box 36)
      - Zork #2 The Malifestro Quest - Book(s) (Box 36)
      - Zork #1 The Forces of Krill - Book(s) (Box 36)
  - Subseries 5: Infocom
    - Infocom Marketing: Announcements / Promotions (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Infocom Marketing: Manuals (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Infocom Marketing: Ads and Ad Copy (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Infocom Marketing: Product Catalogs (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Infocom R-Mode Editor (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Infocom Documentation - Emacs and Unix (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Zork Interlogic (ZIL) Engine (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Infocom Notes on Other Companies Games (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Infocom Notes on Potential Games (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Infocom Notes on Actual Infocom Games (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Infocom Sales Data (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Infocom Production Sundays (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Infocom Development Schedules (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Infocom Notes on Company Move (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Infocom Misc. - Old Phone Lists (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Infodope (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Infocom Memos 1983-1989 (8 folders) (Box 5, Folders 1-8)
    - Infocom Scoremaster Event (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Infocom Tradeshows: CES 5/1987, May 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Infocom Tradeshows: CES 6/1986, June 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Infocom Tradeshows: CES 6/1984, June 1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Infocom Tradeshows: COMDEX 11/1984, November 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Infocom Tradeshows: Apple II Forever 4/1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Infocom Tradeshows: Softcon 2/1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Infocom Hacks and Events (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Infocom Bulletin Board Hacks (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Infocom Misc. - Archival (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Infocom Misc. - Activision Related (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Infocom Misc. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Infocom Reunion - Venue Information (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Zork Interlogic Engine Design Documentation (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Infocom Reunion - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Infocom Reunion - Address Updates (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Infocom Reunion - Great Postcard Campaign (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Infocom Reunion Directory (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Infocom Misc. - Media Lab (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Infocom Planning Meals (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Infocom Marketing: Releases and Articles - 9/1985, September 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Infocom Marketing: Releases and Articles - 9/1984, September 1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Infocom Cornerstone Marketing Releases and Articles (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Infocom Employee Information (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Infocom Marketing: Press Releases and Articles - 1985 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Infocom Marketing: Releases and Articles - 7/1988, July 1988 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Infocom Family Computing Advertisement (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 6: Magic of Xanth
    - Magic of Xanth (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 7: Newsletters
    - New Zork Times / The Status Line Work: Puzzle Stuff (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - New Zork Times / The Status Line Work: Cartoon Stuff (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - New Zork Times / The Status Line: Misc. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters: New Zork Times / The Status Line (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters: InfoCommunique / Off the Record (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Newsletters: Activision, Ink. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - New Zork Times Cartoons: "A" Cartoons (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - New Zork Times Cartoons: Plagiarized Cartoons (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - New Zork Times Cartoons: Printed in The Status Line (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - New Zork Times Cartoons: Well-drawn but Not Funny (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - New Zork Times Cartoons: "B" Cartoons [1 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - New Zork Times / The Status Line
    - New Zork Times Cartoons: "B" Cartoons [2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - New Zork Times / Infodope / The Status Line (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 8: Planetfall Novels
    - Planetfall Novels: Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Planetfall Novels: Stationfall - Drafts (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Planetfall - Books (Box 36)
    - Planetfall Novels: Planetfall Book 1 - Drafts (2 folders) (Box 3, Folders 5-6)
  - Subseries 9: THQ Games
    - THQ Games - Shadowrun MMORPG (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - THQ Games - M-Z (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - THQ Games - A-L (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 11: World of Zoo
    - World of Zoo - Anteater - Giraffe (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - World of Zoo - Gorilla - Zebra (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 12: Playthrough Notes
    - Playthrough Notes - Critical Path (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Playthrough Notes - Shannara (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Playthrough Notes - Might and Magic III (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Playthrough Notes - Might and Magic VII (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Playthrough Notes - Clouds of Xeen (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Playthrough Notes - Darkside of Xeen (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Playthrough Notes - Death Gate (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Playthrough Notes - Might and Magic II (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Playthrough Notes - Myst (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Playthrough Notes - Frederik Pohl's Gateway (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Playthrough Notes - Might and Magic VIII (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Errata - CSI Playthrough Notes - Casual Connect 2009 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Playthrough Notes - Might and Magic VI (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Playthrough Notes - Gateway II Homeworld (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Playthrough Notes - Return of the Incredible Machines (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 13: Conference Materials
    - 2008 Game Developers' Conference Complete Audio Recordings - audio tapes (Box 37)
    - 2003 Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings: Game Design (Box 37)
    - 2003 Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings: Game Audio (Box 37)
    - 2002 Game Developers Conference Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 2003 Game Developers Conference Proceedings (Box 37)
    - Audio for 1995 CGDC - Steve Meretzky
    - 2002 Game Developers Conference Audio Recordings (Sessions 41-80) (Box 37)
    - 1998 Computer Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 2001 Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 1999 Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 1998 Computer Game Developers Conference Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 1997 Computer Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 1996 Computer Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 1995 Computer Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 1994 Computer Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 1993 Computer Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - 1992 Computer Game Developers Conference Audio Proceedings (Box 37)
    - Computer Game Developers' Conference Directory 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Computer Game Developers' Conference Program 1989-1995 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Computer Game Developers' Conference Program 1996-1999 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Computer Game Developers' Conference Program 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Computer Game Developers' Conference Program 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - 1991 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 1992 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 1993 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - 1994 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - 1995 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - 1996 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 44)
    - 1997 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 45)
    - 1998 Computer Game Developers' Proceedings (Box 45)
    - 1999 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 46)
    - 2000 Computer Game Developers' Proceedings (Box 46)
    - 2001 Computer Game Developers' Conference Proceedings (Box 47)
  - Subseries 14: Hintbooks
    - Z System, The (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Infocom Invisiclues Hintbooks B - Planetfall (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Infocom Invisiclues Hintbooks Plunderhearts - Witness (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Infocom Invisiclues Zork and Spellcasting 101, 201, 301 Hintbooks (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 15: Concept Art
    - Character Art - Space Bar (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Reverse Alien Cover Art (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Maps - Space Bar (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Environment Sketches - Space Bar (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Extra Character Sketches (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 16: Posters
    - MDL Programming Language Primer (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - MDL Programming Language (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - MDL Programming Language Environment (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Casual Connect Magazine Summer 2007-2009 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Casual Games Market Report (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - BAGEL System (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Unused Infocomix Binder Tabs (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Bloodliners - Final Design Script (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Coffee Break Collection (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Rex Nebular - Johnny's Ship (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Afterhours (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Zork Users Group - Infocom Game Maps (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Zork - TRS-80 Model I (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Zork Calendar and Zork Coin (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Instruction Manual Proofs - Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy and Leather Goddesses of Phobos (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - IGDA Casual Games Quarterly - Spring 2008-2009 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Hackers (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Dub / Big Trouble (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Dream World / REM States (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Zork Users Group (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Rex Nebular Manual (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Return to Zork (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Spellcasting 101: World Map (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Lane Mastodon - Advertisment Poster (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Fantastic Creatures Print (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Series 5: Born-digital Materials